(Production Sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism and KOCCA)
(This is a work of fiction. All names, characters, )
(and incidents are products of the author's imagination.)
(All child actors were accompanied by a guardian, )
(and filmed in accordance with labour laws.)
It hurts!
Why have you stopped? Keep torturing her!
Oh, dear.
What are we going to do?
Gosh, how wicked.
I am asking you a question! Is this grotesque object yours?
It is not!
I do not know.
You... you insolent wench. Are you saying it is not yours?
I do not know. I really do not know!
Then you do not care what happens to it?
You cannot do that. What a waste.
My goodness, it looks like a man's member.
That precious thing. How could they do that?
It is moving. Hey, it is moving!
- It is vibrating! - Is this thing possessed?
I shall use this on your body, this way and that.
I will test it out myself...
The Secret Royal Inspector is here!
My goodness! It is a Horse Pass. A Horse Pass?
A Horse Pass. A Horse Pass. A Horse Pass.
A Horse Pass.
It was not me. No, oh my.
- What is going on? - That hurts.
Hit him harder!
How dare you strike a nobleman?
Hit him harder, harder!
Gosh.
Darn it!
What the...
Make way for the Secret Royal Inspector!
The Secret Royal Inspector is handsome.
He reminds me of my younger self.
A real flower boy.
Young Lady. Now that I am here,
you have nothing to worry about.
My, he is so handsome.
"Ready? Just trust me now."
What is that sound?
- What is that strange sound? - Young Lady, what is this wicked...
- I think it is from over here. - My Lord.
"Should we go a little harder?"
- My Lord, that sound was not me. - Gosh.
Pretty sure it is.
"Hot Guys Moaning" mode will play next.
It's coming from you.
- I am dying of shame... - See? The sound is coming from her.
Rather than die of humiliation...
Just kill me!
(LOVE.exe)
(Episode 9: Dropping the Course)
Seriously? What was that?
Total humiliation. If that were me, I'd have checked the Han River temp.
- What? Are they talking about me? - So then what happens?
The hero falls off a cliff. It's awesome.
- A cliff? You love when heroes die. - But only you think it's fun.
- Not true. Everyone loves that. - They're not talking about me.
- You saw the Everytime thing? - You mean Dildo Girl?
A CompSci major in my gen-ed class told me it's totally real.
If you blur her face, do it right. What even is that?
The half-assed job just makes her look more pathetic.
That video was hilarious, though.
Typical beta male, loving to see a girl humiliated.
Hey! No, it's not that. The video is just objectively funny.
- Campus Dildo Princess. - That dildo is huge.
- Reporting her. She broke a rule. - Dildo Girl, and Kang Min Hak?
- A sex toy at school is too much. - Her trying to explain is a joke.
She should've left. Why explain?
For your information, she's the top CompSci student.
What is this... What is all this?
Excuse me. This must be tough for you.
Pardon?
I'm one of Min Hak's juniors.
This whole situation is pretty messed up.
Oh. Right.
Of all people to get mixed up with, it had to be a celebrity.
That must make it even tougher on you.
So, did he really have no idea what was inside?
You're saying Kang Min Hak knew?
No.
I'm heading to an event right now.
Today I started off with Jayjun's New Salmon Ampoule again...
to get my skin back in shape. And thanks to the PDRN in it,
it soothes damaged skin right away.
(You were great in the video)
(His biceps catching Dildo Girl were insane)
(That girl is totally getting cancelled)
(What's that got to do with Min Hak?)
I have to get going now, so I'm ending the stream here.
Bye everyone!
Hey, people are saying San is done for.
She's the Quiz King, not a celeb. It's embarrassing, but it'll pass.
If anything, you're the one who should be pissed off.
You're getting dragged into this whole "Dildo Girl" thing,
and they're leaving nasty comments. You have a great reputation.
That's why you get the benefit of the doubt.
Come on, man, don't you start talking like that.
There's nothing going on between you and the Quiz King, right?
It's not like that.
Right? I didn't think so.
A video of a woman in her twenties throwing a sex toy...
in a lecture hall went viral. If that were you, would you be okay?
Human social conventions are so exhausting.
- Trivial reason to drop class. - Trivial?
Are you familiar with the term "self-fulfilling prophecy?"
So, the idea that one's expectations cause them to act in ways...
that makes them come true? A psychology term, right?
Or in many myths, when someone hears the prophecy he'll kill his father.
And every extraordinary action they take to avoid it...
is what ironically leads them to actually killing their father.
Sometimes, the harder you try to avoid someone,
the closer you can ironically become.
Like a dildo hidden in a Banana Pouch.
But what does any of that have to do with my situation?
Human creativity takes a bad situation...
and makes it truly messed up.
Have you seen the view count?
Looking at the data alone,
some people would pay good money for that kind of attention.
How ironic!
I'm not an attention seeker. It's not a form of buzz marketing.
That phrase is so stale.
Buzz marketing.
That vibrations in a medium influence consumer desire...
is just common sense. It's like saying water is wet.
What's more interesting is destructive wave interference.
When one wave...
meets a perfectly opposing wave, they cancel each other out.
Destructive interference. Offset interference.
- These waves... - Are you trying to comfort me?
Or is this some new form of secondary victimization?
I don't subscribe to such extreme value judgments.
Value isn't a fixed definition. It isn't.
It's fluid. It's constantly changing.
Of course,
I'm not denying the pressure that comes from societal perception.
It's just that Korean society is one where a young woman...
expressing her own sexual desires...
is considered taboo. That's the kind of society it is.
Unless you declare you're done for,
you are not done for.
If you go and declare it,
it's a self-fulfilling prophecy, and then you're really done for.
If you want to adopt that narrative and truly be screwed,
then that's just your own choice...
Can you please stop saying all the curse words?
Okay. That abdominal breathing, that was good.
When stressed, using this breathing to pass air over the vocal cords...
is good for your parasympathetic nerve.
A more dynamically-sound solution than dropping the class, right?
If you're done.
Some psycho actually did it.
This school is getting more and more grotesque.
Gosh, who put this up?
San's long-winded explanation just provoked everyone more.
Hey, you're here.
- Are you okay? Are you okay? - I hear the food's good today.
Let's go to the cafeteria. Come on.
They used superglue on this. Gosh.
- It's the meat special today. - Meat special. A meat...
Good grief. Look, your bag's wide open. Take it off.
What? Your hoodie is on inside out, too.
Take it off. You're so spaced out, Joo Yeon San.
- Joo Yeon San, pull up your pants. - My pants?
Look at this. You're wearing mismatched socks again.
Put this on. You really haven't been yourself since that day.
Can't blame you, though.
A dildo flew across the middle of the classroom, after all.
Hey, don't talk about the dildo in front of her.
You're the one who brought it up.
No, I didn't.
You haven't eaten yet, have you? Come on, let's go get some food.
- You must be starving. Let's go. - You were so cool in the lecture.
- Min Hak, hey! - Hi!
Hey.
- Hey, Joo Yeon San. - Where are you going?
- What? - Hey, I said let's go eat!
Hey!
- Hey, San! - Hey, Yeon San, are you okay?
San!
- Hey, leave her alone! - Help me.
Move, move, move!
- You okay? - I'm okay. Thank you.
Unbelievable.
- Joo Yeon San? - Joo Yeon San!
Hey, isn't that Dildo Girl? Right, Dildo Princess.
- She's always mixed up with dildos. - That must be so humiliating.
Joo Yeon San.
I wonder if she's okay.
Feeling guilty?
If only I hadn't tried to give it back to her during class.
It's not like you did it on purpose.
If only I hadn't grabbed her from behind like that.
It's not your fault. You only tried to keep her from falling.
If only I hadn't held on to her for so long.
Enough. Min Hak!
This is a small, dinky school in the boonies outside of Seoul.
Unless the school tries to pull off some ridiculous merger,
nothing exciting ever happens here.
Everyone's desperate for some drama.
But her getting involved with you, the biggest celebrity on campus...
- it's just really bad luck. - True.
Right.
What if I show this to San?
Don't you think it might make her feel better?
What? Let me see. How is this supposed to...
Make her feel better by looking at your face?
No, the next page.
(Healthy, Honest, and Bold!)
Female Masturbation Special.
I actually learned a lot reading this.
Apparently, 97.1 percent of women have experience with masturbation,
and a good number of them use toys.
What if we show her it's not her, but those mocking her for her toy.
That they're the weird ones?
I figured San would be convinced by the numbers.
Min Hak.
Why do you think a magazine would run a special feature on this?
That they'd use so much page space to change perceptions means...
It means that most people still consider this issue...
something to be embarrassed about, don't you think?
- I see. - Being open about it's great.
In this case, the situation is a bit...
more complicated.
I tend to overreact, don't I?
Whenever you're around,
people's first instinct is to pull out their phones.
Look, midterms are next week. This'll blow over once exams start.
Quiet down, my foot.
(Did you guys see Dildo Girl?)
(So freaking gross!)
(Such a perv. Makes me wanna puke.)
(- Look at Professor Eum's face! - I'd expel a student for that.)
Find the average settlement amount for suing over malicious comments.
And the legal fees, too.
(For malicious comments lawsuits, )
(here are the costs.)
(From thousands to over ten thousand dollars)
Ten thousand dollars?
Best countries for a Korean woman in her 20s whose life is ruined,
and calculate the cost and time it would take to relocate.
(That would depend on your criteria for "a good country to live in.")
Gosh, forget about some grand plan.
Just tell me how to clear my head.
Preferably for free.
(Here are a few free ways to clear your head.)
(Four. Meditation and breathing. Five. Go outside.)
(Even simple activities can help.)
So, you mean manual labour?
So you're taking a break from school?
- Yes. - No experience at an internet cafe?
Think you can handle it your first time?
Yes. Troubleshooting boot issues, network failures,
or reinstalling Windows is a piece of cake for me.
- I'm great at cable management. - I'm afraid you'll steal my GPUs.
- Pardon? - Never mind! Can you cook at all?
What?
Payment complete.
(Order Delivered)
Hey, boss! Delivery's here!
The fresh catch has arrived.
- It's a fish. - Yeon San, can you prepare sashimi?
Sashimi?
You're kidding, right?
I'm serious. It's on our menu.
- A new menu item. - A new item?
Yeon San, life is the real deal. And a gaming cafe is a battlefield!
(These are just sound and visual effects)
(The flounder was safely released into the waters off Incheon)
(A few days later)
(Moby Dick)
- So, where is it? - For ten bucks, it's a steal.
Seriously? You put the test bank in a binder?
You could've just shared them on a drive.
It means this test bank is legendary.
What? But where's Professor Eum Nan Sae's test bank?
- It's not here. - Her class has no test bank.
- Why not? Is it too old? - No, her class never had one.
Are you trying to rip me off? That's the most important one!
You clearly don't know. A test bank for her class is no use.
Her exam questions are, well, they're basically random numbers.
Random?
But even random numbers are values pulled from a predetermined range.
- Gosh, you scared us! - What are you doing here?
Is this really how you guys operate?
I'm so close to reporting you for sharing old exams.
Hey, chill out.
So what are Professor Eum's exams like?
With her, you can't gauge the scope. Her tests are impossible to predict.
Back then, I had no idea either. I really didn't.
When everyone, myself included, let their guard down,
that's when Eum Nan Sae's "Exam Chaos" began.
What's with this sudden true-crime doc vibe?
The year was ten years ago, during midterms.
So, Professor Eum starts handing out Post-it notes to the students.
Write down a single number.
The closer your number is to two-thirds...
of the average of all your numbers,
the higher your score will be.
But there was a deeper meaning behind her question.
She hoped they'd team up, write zero,
and create a win-win situation.
But not a single person figured it out.
And then there was the "open book" case.
She said it was open-book, so we brought tons of material...
"How?"
That single word was the entire test.
They say someone just wrote "Wow" and got a perfect score, but...
Given Professor Eum Nan Sae's vibe, you can totally believe that, right?
Gosh, seriously?
And then, the year I started, right before the pandemic hit,
she finally gave a question that was related to our major.
Write a science fiction short story about humans and AI interacting.
Is this a creative writing class? That actually sounds awesome.
That means she can grade it however she wants.
Turns out she did briefly mention it in class at some point.
I never imagined that the professor, who became a legend, would return.
(Jinny and Timothy Confirm Relationship)
(Agency: They have mutual feelings and are getting to know each other.)
Min Hak?
Ji No. Hey.
I wondered why I hadn't seen you. It's because you're all covered up.
I guess you're in a tight spot about the Joo Yeon San incident?
- What? - Are you busy? Can we talk?
I still can't wrap my head around why you chose Joo Yeon San over me.
But I bet you're regretting it by now.
So I'm giving you one more chance. A chance to join my team.
What are you...
I happen to be planning an app that's perfect for you.
A tailored service for influencers called Very Berry.
Very Berry's main function is to analyse public sentiment.
From online communities and social media,
it categorizes sentiment in words used to describe a specific target,
giving you the Strawberry Index. The "Berry Index," for short.
- So if I... - It's a Rotten Tomatoes knock-off.
It's different. We analyse sentiment in detail, positive, negative...
into a whopping 30 different categories.
Min Hak, check this out.
Only the top one percent can earn a Golden Strawberry.
Let's run your name on Very Berry on the biggest Moms' Cafe?
(Kang Min Hak)
(Overwhelmingly Positive Response. Sexy 44 percent, Friendly 35...)
No way, a Golden Strawberry. I've never actually seen one.
You really are a major celebrity.
The nickname sounds weird, but it's short for Golden Strawberry.
In that case, could you maybe search for Joo Yeon San?
Of course. For her, I should search the school forums. Hold on.
(Joo Yeon San)
Nothing's coming up?
You're right.
Most people don't use her real name. Let me try a different keyword.
The term they usually use to refer to her is...
Dildo Girl.
(Dildo Girl)
Whoa, a Rotten Strawberry.
I never thought I'd see one of these in person.
Is it that serious?
This is just a Rotten Strawberry, one that's completely inedible.
Beyond saving. A complete write-off.
The problem is, if you get tied up with Joo Yeon San on the forums,
your Strawberry Index could drop too.
What if we Golden Strawberries unite and try to do something big?
I know, but I'm prepping to transfer to Seoul National University.
A Golden Strawberry in the making, you could say?
(Hangang University)
- Na Rae, did you see these posts? - What?
Doesn't this jerk ever quit?
You've seen them too.
I keep reporting him, but his account is never suspended.
Should I try contacting the site admins?
Or what if we sue for defamation?
Hey, Min Hak.
- It's been a while. - Hey, Dong Won.
You texted Joo Yeon San about the midterms, right?
She hasn't read it. You don't think she's really dropping out, right?
When was the last time we saw Joo Yeon San?
The day with the dildo on the ceiling?
So she hasn't been to school for a week now?
Should we file a missing person report?
- What? You don't think so? - No, that's not it.
She just read it. Just now.
She reads them. She just doesn't reply.
Let's send her something she has to reply to.
Not stuff like, "Where are you?" or "Are you okay?"
Like what?
Joo Yeon San.
Is it okay if we delete our GitHub repo?
(GitHub: Code hosting, Repo: Repository)
That'll get a call right away.
It's no big deal. It just means resetting the repo.
That sounds like a huge deal.
Or...
San, sending a link with some vital info.
"17 Proofs the Earth Is Flat."
She'll never be able to let that go.
San, want to hear about my crush on the guy who lives next door?
The sad part is, he can never love me back.
That's nothing new for you.
Min Hak, you should send one too. You really know how to piss her off.
- Me? - Yes.
That thing you do, that bright-eyed innocence?
Something absurd enough to make her rush back to school to confront you?
What you do best. Sorry.
I don't know...
All that head-in-the-clouds stuff you always say so casually.
Sorry.
I can't just think of something on the spot like that.
That crazy bastard posted again.
With all this drama still going on, Joo Yeon San would never show up.
And what's even more infuriating is his awful spelling.
Send me the link. I'll report it too.
I think I'm going to have to look into getting a lawyer.
Wait a second. What's Joo Yeon San's other class?
Basic Spanish?
But she said the only other person from CS in that class is San.
The first post went up during Professor Eum's class,
so Professor Eum's class and the Database class...
the culprit must be in both classes, right?
Hey, Ban Ji No!
I knew you were lame, but not this vicious.
What are you talking about?
It's you who keeps posting about "Dildo Girl" on the school site.
Besides Professor Eum's class today, she only has one other major class,
Database.
And yet, the culprit knew she skipped class today.
Come on, plenty of people are in both of those classes.
Hey, that's you too, isn't it?
Yes, I'm in both of those classes with her too.
Exactly.
Nine students, both male and female, have both classes,
Five of them are in the background of the photo.
Which means they couldn't have taken the picture themselves.
Two others were off campus today for military reserve training.
That leaves just two people. But the culprit missed one thing.
- The culprit? - The Coke you're drinking now.
Look at the "Dildo Princess" photo. There's a Coke on the desk, see?
Yuseon has type one diabetes.
Even at parties back in our freshman year,
she was known for only drinking water.
Most importantly, you have a motive. A very clear motive.
You're still salty about losing at Quiz King,
and you lost Kang Min Hak from the group.
Just come clean and say you're sorry.
This is all just your speculation.
Do you have any hard evidence?
Of course we do.
If I comment on your Everytime post like this...
What?
- A comment notification? - See? He's getting notifications.
- This is... - Enough. Before I sue for libel,
take down every single post.
Wait...
Hey.
Looks like another post about San just went up.
Judging by the typos, it's the same person.
What, did you set up a bot to post them automatically?
I didn't do it. If you're so sure, just check my Everytime account.
How can you accuse me like that just from a single notification?
This spelling here. Guess it wasn't him.
Then why did you get a notification when I commented?
Because I'm following all the posts about Joo Yeon San.
I was just collecting data I need for Very Berry,
and checking to make sure everything was working right.
I can't believe you used San to develop your app.
Whatever. My conscience is clear.
I won't forget this humiliation. Just you wait.
And Kang Min Hak, I'm really disappointed in you.
Guys, let's go.
(Hangang University)
Isn't improv class kind of hard?
I think it's better than that "write about a wall" assignment.
So absurd...
that she'd come running back to campus.
Was what I said that unbelievable? What else is just as absurd?
Words that...
Hey, you okay?
Things are blowing up on Everytime.
When you get famous, all the weirdos come crawling out.
The CS kids always seemed creepy. And she's the valedictorian, right?
- Queen of the Creeps. - She's my friend.
Watch what you say.
Right, what I meant was, the people linking you to Dildo Girl...
and posting weird comments, they're the jerks, right?
Look,
That dildo isn't Dildo Girl's... Gosh.
My friend...
It's not my friend's. It's just, for a part-time job...
It's...
Anyway, it's just a thing. Unlike us, engineering students...
do part-time jobs with electronics and stuff.
It's weirder for a student's job to involve that kind of thing.
Regardless, she's not hurting anyone.
So let's stop ganging up on her and harassing her like this.
Right, let's stop talking about her. He must be tired of all this.
- It's not like he's not involved... - Something absurd...
Hey, did you hear? Timothy and Jinny are dating.
No way. He's way out of her league.
Are you blind? She's way out of his league.
- No. Timothy's the one trending. - Hello? Jinny is world-class.
PC use by minors is prohibited after 10pm.
Can I see your IDs, please?
- Ma'am, hold on. - I'm in my promos!
- I'm a slave to my promos! - It's my promotion match!
- I can't let you. - Ma'am, come on. Just a bit longer.
It's no big deal.
No. If I get shut down, will you take responsibility?
- Shut down? - Will you?
Just a little longer...
- Time to go. - Gosh.
That girl is such a robot.
(Agency: They have mutual feelings and are getting to know each other.)
(Please send your support and wishes to the new couple.)
(Jinny and Timothy have confirmed it.)
People are so obsessed with other people's lives.
(Min Hak: I have something to tell you)
I have something to tell you.
I haven't seen you around school lately.
You doing okay, Joo Yeon San?
I wonder if Kang Min Hak is doing okay.
In modern society, what is one's most important asset?
Reputation. Whether it's good or bad,
we live in a world where how others see you matters most.
Our influencer-tailored service, Very Berry,
shows you what your reputation is on social media...
through our Strawberry Index. The highest is Golden Strawberry,
down to the lowest level, the Rotten Strawberry.
A few days ago, during the commotion in the Computer Engineering class,
we all saw our school's first-ever Rotten Strawberry, didn't we?
You all remember that, right?
Gosh, that son of a gun.
But even this Rotten Strawberry, if you manage and monitor it,
can be levelled up. But if Dildo Girl can pull it off...
Has he lost his mind? Ban Ji No! Hey, shut up!
However, I'm confident.
- With Very Berry... - You there, shut your mouth!
I can tell what kind of strawberry you are...
without Very Berry, Ban Ji No.
You. You're always telling stories that no one will remember...
and dragging them on for as long as possible.
I bet 99 percent of the students here think you're a total jerk.
What, are you dissing my app just because your rep took a hit?
Besides, your opinion is irrelevant.
But isn't what Very Berry shows just other people's opinions?
If that's the case, my opinion is just another data point.
You yourself don't actually care about other people's opinions,
yet you send your users on a rollercoaster of fickle opinions.
How's that for a contradiction?
And that is my personal assessment of Very Berry and its creator.
- San! - Why didn't you answer our calls?
Why didn't you pick up?
- I was busy. - But you really told him off.
- Right? - He was pissing me off.
San.
What did you want to talk about?
What?
You texted me, remember? You said you had something to say.
It's nothing.
But...
it's good to see you.
A self-fulfilling prophecy.
When trying hard to not get involved is what creates a special bond.